

Contact



027 727 7463



andrewgkeatinge@gmail.com



Hamilton, New Zealand

Skills

React

Node.js

JavaScript

TypeScript

HTML

CSS

Databases & SQL query

API integration

E-commerce

Google Ads

Meta Ads

Adobe Creative Suite

Inventory Management

Microsoft Office

References

References on request

Andrew Keatinge

Web Development / Category Management / Digital Marketing

About

I have been interested in tech my whole life, right from the moment I played on a Gameboy for the first time, and I remember thinking I had never seen anything like it.

I spent a good chunk of the beginning of my career under the delusion that I was going to own a supermarket and be a millionaire! In saying that, I don't have a single regret as working in an environment like a supermarket I picked up a lot of skills a long that way that I believe will be beneficial to a career in tech. However, I have now woken up and realise I am far better off in the pursuit of something I am passionate about.

To this day I often think of that moment I held the Gameboy and how it opened up my mind to the possibilities that tech can create. I have spent the last few years working my way towards a tech career. My aim is to one day be part of something that becomes someone else's Gameboy moment.

Recent Projects

Toolr - https://github.com/karaka-2024/toolr

The idea of this app was a tool-share concept where users could rent / borrow tools from people in the areas around them. Due to the time constraints the app wasn't completed fully, however we did manage to pack in a fair bit of functionality.

Using tech to solve problems

I have used my new coding skills to fix some of the problems I have had in my existing job. Here are some examples.

Loading products on to our website

This process involves getting relevant product data in a .csv format and uploading it to our website. There is an appliance buying group in Australia called Narta and I was able to connect to their API and work the data to be downloaded in the same format as our website takes significantly reducing the time required to complete this job.

You can see it here: https://nexus.pushed.nz/

Price Matching

Being price competitive vs the market is one of the requirements of my category management role. This is quite a time consuming job as I need to visit each stores website for each product. I am still wanting to work to refine this but I have started on a couple of scripts to crawl over some of our competitor's websites to return their current pricing. This has been immensely helpful and freed up time to focus on other jobs.

I played around using Python for this.

https://github.com/Drewkeatinge/price-matching



Contact



027 727 7463



andrewgkeatinge@gmail.com



Hamilton, New Zealand

Interests

Stand-up Comedy

Video Games

Cinema

Motorcycles

Photography

Links

https://github.com/Drewkeatinge



https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-keatinge/



Andrew Keatinge

Web Development / Category Management / **Digital Marketing**

Experience

Dev Academy

Feb 2024 - Oct 2024

- Over 800+ hours of coding experience.
- Huge focus on group work and pair / team programming.
- Simulated work environment using agile methodology.
- Human skills such as giving / receiving feedback, empathy, awareness, active listening, self-compassion & avoiding bias.

Heathcotes

June 2018 - Present

- **Notable Achievements**
 - Optimised the online dispatch process reducing a required team of 6 down to 3.
 - o Implemented fraud rules reducing fraud attempts to almost zero. 0 bank driven chargebacks in the last year
 - Implemented new pricing system so the business can react to the market quicker
- Skills
 - Website content management.
 - Manage website development projects.
 - Digital marketing.
 - Category management.
 - Business process optimisation
 - **Problem Solving**
 - Relationship building
 - Negotiation

FMCG

2003 - 2018

- Leadership / mentorship
- Team management
- Relationship building
- Negotiation

Education

Dev Academy

Feb 2024 - Oct 2024

Distance

Level 6 certificate in applied software development

Massey University - Ongoing

2020 - 2022

Distance - Bachelor of Information Sciences

Completed papers:

- 157151
- 247112
- 161111

- 158120
- 157240
- 158235

- 158258
- 159172

158359